ometria.com 2017-09-14

# Privacy Policy | Ometria

#### Ometria Ltd ("we," “us” or “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, use and share information which identifies you or is associated with you ("personal information").

#### Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. By setting up an account with us or using and accessing www.ometria.com (the “Service”), you consent to the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Omteria Ltd. Our registered office is at 9th Floor, 107 Cheapside, London, United Kingdom EC2V 6DN. Our company registration number is 08372083.

#### You should also be aware that we use cookies to store and access information whilst providing the Service. You can find out more about our use of cookies in our Cookie Policy.

  1. ##### 1\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT.

##### We collect categories of information set out in sections a. and b. below

    * ##### a. Information we collect directly from you:

##### We collect information from you when you voluntarily submit information to us or the Service. The following are examples of when we may collect information directly from you:

      * When you fill in and submit forms on the Service, including forms submitted at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material, reporting a problem with the Service or requesting further information from us. 

      * When you contact us via online submission, telephone, electronic mail or regular mail, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

      * When you to complete surveys via the Service. 

      * When you engage in transactions through the Service and submit information for the fulfilment of your orders. 

      * When you post comments to us on the Service or third party website where we have a profile or presence. 

##### Examples of information we collect may include: name, address, telephone number, email address, financial information such as payment details and your transactional history with us, comments, opinions and correspondence you share with us.

    * ##### b. Information about how you use the Service

##### We collect data about how you use the Service such as the pages and links you access, searches you make, the time you access the Service and duration you are on it, the site you come to the Service from or go to after leaving the Service, selections and choices you make and preferences that you set when using the Service.

    * ##### c. Information about how you connect to the Service

##### We collect data about the computer or other electronic device (“device”) you use to connect to the Service such as details about the type of device (which can include unique device identifying numbers), its operating system, browser and applications connected to the Service through the device, your Internet service provider or mobile network, your IP address and your devices telephone number (if it has one).

    * ##### d. Information about your actual location

##### We do not collect information about your actual location, other than an approximate location (usually no more precise than city level) which can be determined from your IP address. In certain instances we may use cookies and similar technologies to store and access information we collect through the Service. You can find out more about our use of cookies in our Cookie Policy.

  2. ##### 2\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

##### The information we collect directly from you, about how you use the Service and about how you connect to Service may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who works for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By using the Service you consent to any transfer, storage or processing of your personal information outside of your country. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

##### All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Service, you are solely responsible for keeping this password confidential. If the password has been stolen or might otherwise be subject to misuse, it is your responsibility to notify us immediately for further action.

##### Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

  3. ##### 3\. USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

##### We use the information we collect in the following ways:

    * To manage your account and provide you with the features of the Service, validate and keep your personal information accurate and handle orders and process payments. We will use information we collect directly from you for this purpose. 

    * To ensure that content from the Service is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device and to display content and features that are tailored to you, your interests and how you use the Service. We will use information we collect directly from you, information about how you use the Service and information about how you connect to the Service for this purpose. 

    * To provide you with information about products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you (in accordance with your marketing preferences). We will use information we collect directly from you for this purpose. 

    * To determine and predict information that may be of interest or relevant to you. We will use information we collect directly from you, information about how you use the Service and information about how you connect to the Service for this purpose. 

    * To carry out our obligations arising from any agreements entered into between you and us. We will use information we collect directly from you, information about how you use the Service and information about how you connect to the Service for this purpose. 

    * To notify you about changes to the Service and address complaints, comments and issues you have in relation to your use of the Service. We will use information we collect directly from you for this purpose. 

    * To prevent, detect and investigate illegal activities, breaches of any agreements entered into between you and us and threats to the security of the Service. We will use information we collect directly from you, information about how you use the Service and information about how you connect to the Service for this purpose. 

    * To produce aggregate statistical information and analytics about users of the Service from which individuals cannot be identified. 

  4. ##### 4\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

##### We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries and the employees, agents, officers, directors and contractors of the foregoing entities. These companies will only use your personal information in the same way as we can under this Privacy Policy.

##### We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

    * Who provide a service to us. These third parties will only be allowed to use your personal information in accordance with our instructions and will be required to keep your information secure. 

    * In the event that we sell or buy or transfer any business or assets (in part or whole), in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller, buyer or recipient of such business or assets. 

    * In order to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal duty or obligation (including without limitations requests or demands from law enforcement and government authorities and regulators). 

    * In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or to prevent financial loss to any person or entity, including Ometria Ltd, its customers, clients, and other parties. 

    * In order to enforce or apply any agreement we have with you. 

    * Business partners who offer a service to you jointly with us. 

  5. ##### 5\. YOUR MARKETING RIGHTS

##### You have the right to ask us not to process the personal information for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [info@ometria.com](mailto:info@ometria.com)

##### We or online advertising networks that we partner with may use cookies to make sure advertisements you see online are more relevant to you. You can find out more about cookies and how to manage them by reading our Cookie Policy.

##### The Service may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

  6. ##### 6\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION

##### The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

  7. ##### 7\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

##### Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

##### We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change any portions of this Privacy Policy, the changes will be updated on this Privacy Policy page. You should periodically review our Privacy Policy page for any such changes. Please further note, depending on your particular interaction with us, different portions of this Privacy Policy may apply to you at different times.

  8. ##### 8\. CONTACT

##### Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [info@ometria.com](mailto:info@ometria.com)

##### Last updated on 24/05/13

## QUESTIONS? CALL US!

#### We're always ready to answer any of your questions. Call and we will talk you through how our software can help your business grow.

## book a demo

#### Let us walk you through a live demonstration of how the Ometria solution can help you maximise value from your customers and products.
